Farbstein, Leonard; Papers apap245
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- The 89th Congress, 1956-1966; 5; 7.75 cubic ft.
  - Department of the State, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Department of the State: Multilateral Force, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Department of the State: World Organization of Rabbis, Nazi Victims, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Department of Treasury, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Dominican Republic, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Drug Addiction, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - "E" Last Names, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Education Aid (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Education Aid (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Education and Labor Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - "F" Last Names, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Federal Aid to Education, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Federal Aid to Education: Congressman Farbstein, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Federal Aid to Education: Congressman Farbstein, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Federal Aid to Education: Congressman Fino, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Federal Aid to Education: Congressman Fino, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Federal Aviation Agency, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Affairs: Anti-Semitism, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Affairs: Arab Refugees, 1963; 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Affairs: China, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Affairs: Egypt, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Affairs: Foreign Affairs Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Affairs: Foreign Aid Bill (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Affairs: Foreign Aid Bill (2 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Foreign Affairs: India, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Foreign Affairs: Israel, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Affairs: Jordan, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Affairs: Middle East, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Foreign Affairs: Near East Report, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Foreign Affairs: North Korean Incident, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Foreign Affairs: Proposed Legislation, 1963; 1966 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Foreign Affairs: Soviet Anti-Semitism (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Foreign Affairs: Soviet Anti-Semitism (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Foreign Affairs: United Nations, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Foreign Affairs Committee: Notices, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Frank Canaday Correspondence, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - General Correspondence on H.R. 10855, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - General Service Administration, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - H. Con. Res. 89: A Concurrent Resolution for Establishment of an International Living Museum of Anthropology and Ethnography, 1963-1965; 1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - H. Con. Res. 90: A Concurrent Resolution for the Distribution and Viewing of the film "Years of Lightning. Days of Drums." by the United States Information Agency on the Late President Kennedy, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - H. Con. Res. 103: A Concurrent Resolution for the Elimination of Racial Discrimination, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - H. Con. Res. 128: A Concurrent Resolution for Expressing the Sense of the Congress with Respect to Anti-Semitism in the Soviet Union, and Calling Upon the Soviet Union to Guarantee Human Rights, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - H. Con. Res. 152: A Concurrent Resolution for the Establishment of a Joint Committee on the Organization of the Congress, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - H. Con. Res. 306: A Concurrent Resolution for the Strengthening of the United Nations, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - H. Con. Res. 340: A Concurrent Resolution for the Establishment of the United Nations Conciliation Committee, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - H. Con. Res. 384: A Concurrent Resolution for Planning for Peace, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - H. Con. Res. 408: A Concurrent Resolution for Expressing the Sense of the Congress Relative to the Free Exercise of Religion and Pursuit of Culture by Jews and All Others within the Soviet Union, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - H. Con. Res. 473: A Concurrent Resolution for the Recognition of World Law Day, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - H. Con. Res. 967: A Concurrent Resolution for the Establishment of a Branch of the Harry S. Truman Center for the Advancement of Peace for Middle Eastern Students, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - H. J. Res. 133: A Joint Resolution for the Foreign Assistance Act of 1961, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - H. J. Res. 336: A Joint Resolution for the Issuance of a Special Postage Stamp in Commemoration of the Liberation by the United States Armed Forces from the Concentration Camps in Germany in World War II, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - H. J. Res. 466: A Joint Resolution for the Development of Ellis Island as a Part of the Statue of Liberty National Monument, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - H. J. Res. 469: A Joint Resolution for United States Diplomatic Relations with the Republics of Ukraine and Byelorussia (Also Contains H. J. Res. 428), 1963; 1965 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - H. J. Res. 922: A Joint Resolution to Designate the Second Week in May as National School Safety Patrol Week, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - H. J. Res. 1094: A Joint Resolution to Create a Delegation to a Convention of North Atlantic Nations, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - H. J. Res. 1174: A Joint Resolution for Economic Opportunity Act of 1964, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - H. R. 448: A Bill for Prevention of Construction of Nuclear Devices, 1963; 1965 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - H. R. 993: A Bill for Amendment of the Clayton Act (Also Contains Related Bills), 1962-1963; 1965 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - H. R. 994: A Bill for Amendment of the Civil Service Retirement Act (Also Contains Related Bills), 1961; 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - H. R. 995: A Bill for Coverage of Federal Employees (Also Contains Related Bills), 1958-1959; 1961; 1963; 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - H. R. 3299: A Bill for Amendment of the Immigration and Nationality Act, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - H. R. 3301: A Bill for the Amendment of Title 18 of the United States Code to Provide Immunity, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - H. R. 3451: A Bill for Authorization of the President of the United States to Award Posthumously a Congressional Medal of Honor to John Fitzgerald Kennedy, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - H. R. 3590: A Bill for Hospital Insurance Program, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - H .R. 3703: A Bill for the Amendment of Title 2 of the Social Security Act to Increase Age Limit for Children's Insurance Coverage, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - H. R. 4168: A Bill for the Establishment of the National Humanities Foundation, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - H .R. 4487: A Bill for Amendment of the Federal Water Pollution Control Act, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - H .R. 4772: A Bill for Amendment of the International Claims Settlement Act of 1949 (Also Contains Related Bills), 1962-1963; 1965 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - H. R. 5032: A Bill for Authorization to Use Excess Government-Owned Foreign Currencies to Finance Abroad of Binational Foundations for Educational and Scientific Purposes, 1965; 1967 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - H. R. 5603: A Bill for Amendment of the Export Control Act of 1949, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - H. R. 5923: A Bill for the Further Implementation of the Constitutional Right to Bail, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - H. R. 6250: A Bill for the Establishment of the National Foundation on the Arts and the Humanities, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - H. R. 6306: A Bill for the Presentation of the Bronze Star Medal to Sidney Clinton Stern (Also Contains Related Bills), 1956; 1959; 1961; 1965 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - H. R. 6323: A Bill to Vote Without Discrimination Because of Race or Color, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - H. R. 6878: A Bill for Amendment of the Social Security Act, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - H. R. 6911: A Bill for the Establishment of the Hudson National Scenic Riverway in the States of New York and New Jersey, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - H. R. 7063: A Bill for the Protection of the Right on Individuals to Register to Vote in Elections without Discrimination Because of Race or Color (Also Contains H. R. 6400), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - H. R. 7906: A Bill for Prohibition of the Use of Mail Covers, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - H. R. 7951: A Bill for Deduction for Income Tax Purposes, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - H. R. 8241: A Bill for Establishment of a Program of Grant-in-Aid for the Construction of County Courthouse in the United States, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - H. R. 8618: A Bill for Assistance in the Provision of Housing for Low- and Moderate- Income Families, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - H. R. 8665: A Bill for Federal Inspection of Slaughter for Human Food Purposes, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - H. R. 8689: A Bill for Appropriation of Funds to the Secretary of the Army for the Acquisition of a Building on Fort Jay Military Reservation, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - H. R. 8908: A Bill for Civil Commitment in Lieu of Criminal Punishment with Cases Involving Narcotics Addicts (Also Contains Related Bills), 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - H. R. 9726: A Bill for Amendment to the War Claims Act of 1948, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - H. R. 9762: A Bill for Amendment to the Atomic Energy Act of 1954, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - H. R. 9763: A Bill for Amendment to the Urban Mass Transportation Act of 1964, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - H. R. 9959: A Bill for Establishment of the Clinical Laboratory Licensing Act of 1965 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - H. R. 10521: A Bill for Conferment of Jurisdiction in the United States Court of Claims in Regard to Stephen Goodwin, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - H. R. 10855: A Bill for Amendment of the Public Works and Economic Development Act of 1965, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - H. R. 13255: A Bill for Amendment of the Federal Firearms Act (Also Contains Related Bills), 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - H. R. 13520: A Bill for Development of Program in New York and New Jersey to Preserve the Hudson River, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - H. R. 13809: A Bill for Amendment of the Economic Opportunity Act of 1964, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - H. R. 13857: A Bill to Provide a Permanent Special Milk Program for Children, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - H. R. 14638: A Bill for Amendment of the United States Code, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - H. R. 14798: A Bill for the Amendment of the Act of October 10, 1949, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - H. R. 16923: A Bill of the Striking of a Medal in Commemoration of the Designation of Ellis Island as Part of the Statue of Liberty National Monument, 1963-1964; 1966 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - H. R. 16990: A Bill to Stabilize Prices of Food Staples, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - H. Res. 24: A Resolution for Authorization of the Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce to Investigate the Sale of Lethal Firearms, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - H. Res. 145: A Resolution for the Creation of a Select Committee to Conduct an Investigation of the Rate of Cost Increase under Health Benefits (Also Contains Related Bills), 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - H. Res. 684: A Resolution for Nonproliferation of Nuclear Weapons (Also Contains Related Bills), 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - H. Res. 685: A Resolution for Amendment of the Rules of the House of Representatives for the Creation of the Committee of Urban Affairs, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - H. Res. 692: A Resolution for the United States Ratification of the Genocide Convention, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - H. Res. 834: A Resolution for the Proposed Transfer of the Army and Air Force Exchange Services from New York City, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - H. Res. 890: A Resolution for Carrying Out the Economic Opportunity Act of 1964 during the Fiscal Year of 1966 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Housing and Home Financing Agency, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Housing and Home Financing Agency, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Housing and Home Financing Agency: Cooper Square Urban Renewal Area, 1961-1963; 1966 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Internal Revenue Service (Transfer), 1963; 1965 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs Committee, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Iraqi-Kurdistan Situation, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Judiciary Committee, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Office of Economic Development: University Settlement, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Athletic School and American Automotive School, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Cardinal Spellman Center Head Start Program, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Chelsea Area Meeting for Planning (CHAMP), 1966 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Chinatown Planning Council, Inc. Head Start and Youth Program, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: College and Career Consultants, 1965-1968 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Coordination Council on Education for the Disadvantage, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Educational Alliance Project for the Elderly Poor, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Grand Street Settlement House, Inc. Tutorial Project, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Haryou Act, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Hudson Guild, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Hudson Guild Study Den Program, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Knickerbocker Creative Theatre Foundation, Inc., 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Letter to President Johnson Regarding OEO Funds for New York City, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Lincoln Square Neighborhood Center, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Lower East Side Daycare Nursery and New York City Anti-Poverty Board, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Lower Eastside Narcotics Center, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Lower Eastside Neighborhood Association, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Lower Manhattan Anti-Poverty Inc. Community Action Program, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Migrant Grants to States, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Office of Economic Development: Mobilization for Youth, Inc. Lower East Side Economic Development Program, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Operation Head Start, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Project APEX, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Project TIE, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Sea and Land Presbyterian Church, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: St. Teresa's Rectory, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Summer Program Committee from the Community Progress Center of Lower West Side, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Summer Remedial Reading Program, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Office of Economic Development: Two Bridges Neighborhood Council, Inc., 1965 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Two Bridges Neighborhood Council, Inc., 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Two Bridges Neighborhood Council Parent Development Program, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Two Bridges Neighborhood Council, Inc. Proposal for Urban Renewal Project, 1966; 1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity, Two Bridges Neighborhood Council Summer Remedial Reading Program, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: VISTA, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Walter White, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: War Against Poverty Structure Outline, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Yeshivah Umesivtha Torah V' Emunah Oshry, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Peace Corps, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Proposed Legislation on Economic Effect of New York Transit Strike, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Small Business Committee, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Select Committee on National Economic Security, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - State Department Congressional Vietnam Conference Report, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - State Department Publications, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - State Department: Statute of Limitations, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - State Department: Vietnam (1 of 3), 1966 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - State Department: Vietnam (2 of 3), 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - State Department: Vietnam (3 of 3), 1965 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - State Department: Viet Nam, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Subcommittee on Foreign Economic Policy: Background Material on the Kennedy Round, Tariff Negotiations and U.S. Foreign Trade, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Subcommittee on Foreign Economic Policy: Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Un-American Activities Committee, 1962; 1965 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Veteran's Administration, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Veteran's Affairs Committee, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Voting Rights, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Ways and Means, 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - White House (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - White House (2 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- The 90th Congress, 1962-1968; Undated; 6; 12.4 cubic ft.
  The content within this series is arranged alphabetically.
  The records found in this series consist of legislative actions, correspondence with constituents, newspaper clippings, and other subject-specific documents. Such subjects fall under the categories of: Foreign Affairs and various Departments and Committees. There is also documentation of the Office of Economic Opportunity/Emergency Small Loan Program within this series. Within this series are also applications to military academies to be approved by Farbstein. As these materials contain personally identifiable information, these specific files have been restricted.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  - "A" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agency for International Development (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agency for International Development (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Air Force, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Air Force Academic Year 1968-1969 -[RESTRICTED] (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Yes
  - Animal Welfare Act, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Annapolis -[RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Annapolis Academic Year 1968-1969 -[RESTRICTED], 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Appropriations Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "B" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Background Legislation on Poverty Bill (1967) and Emergency Small Loan Program Since Establishment in 1966 (1 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Background Legislation on Poverty Bill (1967) and Emergency Small Loan Program Since Establishment in 1966 (2 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Banking and Currency Committee, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Birth Control Information, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "C" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Civil Disorders, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Civil Rights, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Civil Rights, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Civil Rights: Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., 1968 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Civil Rights: Open Housing Provision, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Civil Rights: Poor People's March on Washington, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Coast Guard Academic Year 1968-1969, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Congressional Ethics (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Congressional Ethics (2 of 2), 1964; 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Copper Workers Strike, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Copyright Revision Bill: H. R. 2512, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "D" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Department of Agriculture, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Department of the Air Force, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Department of the Army, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Department of Commerce (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Department of Commerce (2 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Department of Defense, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare: Adult Career Training, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare: Mobilization for Youth Higher Education Program, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Department of the Interior, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Department of Justice, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Department of Labor, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Department of the Navy, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Department of the State, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Department of the State: Nepal Detention of Ministers, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - District of Columbia Committee, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Draft Revision of Legislation (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Draft Revision of Legislation (2of 2), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Drug Abuse Education Act of 1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - "E" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Economic Opportunity Amendments of 1967 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Economic Opportunity Amendments of 1967 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Economic Opportunity Amendments of 1967 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Economic Opportunity Amendments: Letters from Hamilton-Madison House, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Education and Labor Committee, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Elementary and Secondary Education Amendments of 1967, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Emergency Small Loan Program, 1966; 1968 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Emergency Small Loan Program, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Emergency Small Loan Program Conference Photographs, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Emergency Small Loan Program Conference Report, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Emergency Small Loan Program Correspondence and Newspaper Clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Emergency Small Loan Program and the Economic Opportunity Amendments of 1967 (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Emergency Small Loan Program and the Economic Opportunity Amendments of 1967 (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Emergency Small Loan Program Guidelines, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Emergency Small Loan Program: Robert Dolan Letter, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Committee, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - "F" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Federal Aviation Agency, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Federal Employees Raise, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Federal Power Commission: Air Pollution, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Firearms (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Firearms (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Food and Drug Administration, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Food Stamps Program, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Food Supplement Program, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)